{
    "id": "f0ace77ec7dc49d08e4195326f41c732",
    "title": "Mistakes with verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "560c82047e42413cb9d8b2692276d0ec",
            "title": "Mistakes With Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "All day I was ................................... a sweater.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "putting on",
                        "wearing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ................................... my car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "disposed of",
                        "disposed off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please ................................... this painting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "look at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ................................... a new computer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ordered",
                        "ordered for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why donâ€™t you ................................... me?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "listen to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He came ....................................... a blue jacket.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wearing",
                        "putting on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ...................................... to come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "denied",
                        "refused"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .................................... there for a day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lived",
                        "stayed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .................................. no mistake.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "committed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ought to ............................... exercise.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "make",
                        "take"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}